Hey.
The reason why you hate me so much is cuz
I dropped a washtub on your head, right?
I have no intent
on being chummy with you.
But I don't feel like
being enemies, either.
I went a bit too far that time.
Sorry.
So you, too.
Apologize to Okarun since
you made fun of him.
Then we'll call it even, okay?
You really don't get it at all, Momo Ayase.
I wouldn't call you my sworn enemy
because of a washtub.
I'm after you because I'm positive
that you're a demon!
I told you that I wasn't!
You're nothing but trouble if you poke at me
because of a misunderstanding!
Then what the hell is he!?
Takakura-kun fighting Acrobatic Silky
looked just like a demon.
Besides!
There's no way she's your grandmother!
She's too pretty and way too young!
What's that?
She's a really good girl!
Yeah, Momo is a demon.
You shut up, old hag!
You're complicating things!
I knew it.
Takakura-kun and Auntie are demons.
And you're the big boss in charge of them!
You're trying to destroy the world, I bet.
ARE YOU A TOTAL IDIOT!?
IF I HAD SUCH POWERS, I'D START OFF
BY BLOWING YOUR HEAD OFF!
DON'T GO DAYDREAMING
LIKE SOME EIGHTH GRADER!
BLOW MY HEAD OFF?
NOW YOU'RE SHOWING YOUR TRUE COLORS!
RIGHT NOW, I DON'T HAVE
ENOUGH POWER TO BEAT YOU.
BUT I'M SURE I'LL BECOME STRONGER
AND BEAT YOU!
SOUNDS GREAT! TRY ME IF YOU CAN!
I'LL BEAT YOU TO A PULP!
SOUNDS LIKE YOU UNDERESTIMATE ME,
BUT YOU'RE FORGETTING ONE THING.
I HAVE BEEN CHOSEN
TO PROTECT WORLD PEACE!
Because I'm just too cute!
Thanks for having me!
The somen noodles were tasty, Auntie!
Hold on, damn you!
I'm not done talking to you!
Keep trying hard, Aira.
Blow Momo away!
Auntie here is cheering for you.
Damn it, you old hag!
Why are you rooting for her?
Huh?
Takakura-kun.
Despite being a demon,
you tried to save me multiple times.
Why?
It's because he's not a demon!
I have no reason.
If someone's in trouble,
you'd help them, wouldn't you?
I see.
You still have a human heart left in you.
I will make sure to liberate you
from Momo Ayase's control!
Hey! What was that?
She's got a tremendous misunderstanding.
There's something
seriously wrong with her!
This feeling is so wrong.
I'm a human, and he's a demon.
It's wrong!
Hold on!
Can't you do this a bit more normally!?
Quit your whining.
I'm putting yer ball back in for ya.
Let's play a tight game!
THE POWER OF NESSIE
- And why're you trying to bat?
- Pitcher's jittery! Hey, hey, hey!
Jittery? Who're ya talkin' to?
When you see my Turbo Granny Ball...
you won't be spoutin' such nonsense!
Such cheeky talk!
Strike! Batter out!
When a ball strikes your nuts,
ya gotta jump!
No!
So? Is it back in there?
It's back!
I have one ball back!
- Hurray!
- All right!
That pitch was high and inside.
I'll hit it next time.
Smokin' ball, huh?
Good for you, Okarun.
You got a testicle back.
It's so embarrassing!
That aside...
We have no clues for the other one.
You're right.
Okarun, you don't have a computer?
Can't you look at occult forums
or something?
I'm sorry, I don't have one.
Guess I'll add more part-time jobs
and buy a smartphone.
A four-year loan is a serious rip-off.
So I'll see you at the roof during lunch?
U-Um, I'm sorry, Miss Ayase.
I'd like to work on a report during lunch.
Oh. I see.
Wanna head to an internet café
after school?
I'm sorry. I also have
something after school.
All right. I get it.
I'VE GOT THIS FUNNY FEELING
EPISODE 8
I'm starving.
Let's eat together!
Huh? Where's Okarun?
He said he's working on a report.
So noble! Maybe I'll have him
work on mine, too.
Okarun is so serious.
But it's kinda suspicious.
Huh? What's that?
It's like totally obvious
that he's hiding something.
A scent of a woman?
No.
Okarun's the last person
I'd suspect that, but...
Nah. It couldn't be.
I'm gonna go buy a drink.
Then can you get me one, too?
A Pompy.
POMPY ORANGE
What is this?
I feel so uneasy.
Should I peek into Class C?
No, I don't want to bother him.
He's writing a report after all.
Fourteen... Fifteen... Sixteen...
Seventeen... Eighteen...
Nineteen... Twenty.
I'm no good like this.
As I look for my golden ball,
I'm sure another dangerous monster
will show up, and I'll have to fight it.
Push-ups, sit-ups,
back extensions, and squats.
Five sets, 100 reps each.
I have to become strong.
A lot stronger.
If I don't, I'll be putting
Miss Ayase in harm's way.
Takakura-kun.
Miss Shiratori.
D-Do you need something?
You're a demon, and I'm a human.
I know that it will never be...
I'm not a demon, though.
I can't hold back how I feel!
Takakura-kun! You just stay still!
- Huh? What the...
- Don't move.
- Just close your eyes.
- But...
Hey!
Why are you dodging me?
You're so weird, Takakura-kun!
Wait.
You're the weird one!
Why would you do that out of the blue?
I mean...
I mean, when you confess your love,
you have to kiss that person, right?
Huh!?
It said so in a book!
WEEKLY TRUE ACCOUNTS
FULL NUDE PHOTOS "JUNGLE SPRING"
That confessing equals a kiss!
And that it's the responsibility
of the guy to accept that confession!
That's a mistake!
What did you use as your reference?
U-Um...
ROMANCE MANUAL
VOL.8 (R-18)
It was the one in Dad's study!
That's something completely different!
Miss Shiratori, you're totally popular
with all the boys.
Why are you acting like
you're an amateur in relationships?
- You like mature lips?
- I didn't say that!
Can you stop this?
A popular girl
shouldn't be doing something like this.
Don't equate popularity and romance!
You don't know the effort
behind popularity!
And I'm not an amateur in relationships!
I just don't know about them!
Don't mock me!
That's exactly who the phrase describes!
And right now,
you've got every last thing wrong!
I've never felt this way before.
Let me confess!
A-Are you insane!?
Or are you possessed
by something again?
Hold on, Miss Shiratori.
Um, uh...
Takakura-kun.
Hurry up.
No, wait. This is...
Why you little turd...
Miss Ayase! You got it wrong!
This is nothing like what you think.
You said you were going to work on a report,
but you're making out with that damn girl.
You took your jacket off
and you're even sweating.
What's that on your arms?
Part of your kinky play?
I have reasons for all of this!
I don't want to hear excuses.
Was the report thing a lie?
Th-That was a lie.
I've had enough.
But there's a reason for...
I said, I've had enough!
POMPY ORANGE
Where's my Pompy?
I gave it to the ground.
What's that? A new gag?
They didn't have any?
- Hold on. I'm thinking right now.
- Huh?
STRIKING QUICKLY WITH RAPTORIAL LIMBS,
IT BREAKS CLAMS TO EAT.
DURING TERRITORIAL BATTLES AGAINST
OTHER MANTIS SHRIMP
IS WHEN THEY ALSO UNLEASH PUNCHES.
A mantis shrimp's punches
clock at 80 kilometers per hour.
It has the force of roughly 150 kilograms.
If you scale it to human size,
it's roughly 700 tons.
You can defeat elephants with such a punch.
It's this effective underwater
with all that resistance.
How destructive do you think it'd be
if it was unleashed in air?
Actually, that's still an unknown.
Because a mantis shrimp is thought
to hold back on its punches while in air.
I see, I see. You too have times when
you simply want to punch something.
Perhaps the mantis shrimp realizes that
because its punches have too much force.
She just talked to a mantis shrimp!
Unleashing one in the air may injure
its joints at best, and burst its arm at worst.
She's got it pretty bad.
There is...
...no mistake.
She's been possessed
by the spirit of a mantis shrimp!
Miss Ayase is right about this.
It's pointless to make excuses.
If I'd gotten stronger without
her knowing, I thought it'd be kinda cool.
I even made an effort to lie.
I've sown the seeds myself.
If I care about Miss Ayase,
I shouldn't make excuses,
and just get stronger!
Hey! Is anyone here!?
Miss Shiratori!
Takakura-kun!
Miss Shiratori, where's everyone else?
What's going on?
It's pitch black outside the window.
What happened?
Can this be Momo Ayase's doing?
Come to think, where's Miss Ayase?
Miss Ayase, are you in here?
She's not here.
This feeling... I've experienced
something similar in the past.
Damn it. I'm completely locked in.
This seriously sucks!
The water level is rising, too!
I wonder what happened to Okarun.
Or is this only happening to me?
Sheesh! When I think about him,
I get so pissed off!
What's up with this water, anyway!?
What the...
Something's totally approaching.
What is that? A dinosaur?
Sheesh! Is Okarun not here?
What was that sound?
I don't know.
But it sounded like an explosion.
Hey, what exactly
is this situation we're in?
Are you and Momo Ayase
trying to frame me?
Of course not.
I'd like to ask what's going on myself.
But something similar to this
happened in the past.
It was pitch black outside,
and we were completely walled in.
What did you do back then?
Well, when we defeated the alien,
it went back to normal.
Alien?
Hold on a second. Aliens exist?
They do!
To be honest, they're even worse
than yokai monsters!
Huh? Then why do aliens assault us?
Well, I don't know.
It seems like they're collecting
human reproductive organs.
Chiquitita, you have a dream?
Chi-Chiquitita, Chi-Chiquitita-chi.
Chiquitita. Chiquitita, you have a dream?
Chi-Chiquitita, Chi-Chi-Chiquitita.
Chi-Chi-Chiquitita.
Sh-Shy my chotchiki for you.
This makes me wilt.
Chi-Chiquitita, Chi-Chi-Chiquitita-chi.
Man, what a bother.
Chi-Chi-Chiquitita.
Chiquitita, you have a dream?
It's impossible for me to protect a girl.
Chi-Chi-Chi-Chi-Chiquitita.
Chi-Chi-Chiquitita.
Sh-Shy my chotchiki for you.
Uh, ah, west and east.
Aira-chan. You're in the way, so get lost.
"A-Aira-chan"?
Uh, ah, north and south.
We haven't even kissed yet.
Don't call me that!
Uh, ah, morning, noon, and night.
I feel so droopy.
We're gig workers.
Takakura-kun!
We finally meet, man person.
Serpoians.
Hold on, you guys!
Get away from him!
I will take you on!
Miss Shiratori, run for it!
These guys target women!
Miss Shiratori!
We adjusted this void space so that
only those with high spirituality can enter.
Is the apparatus malfunctioning?
We came here because
we just want your banana organs.
We want it.
Damn it!
Why is everything after my junk?
Because it's something good.
You have an amazing power
that surpasses our scientific technology.
We want your abilities.
We'd love to experiment on you...
...and transplant your abilities to us.
That's the power of a curse.
It's not my own abilities
or anything like that!
I personally have less physical power
than the average person!
Curse? What kind of
banana organ condition is that?
Like I'd know!
Damn it. I can't transform at all.
It feels like when Miss Ayase is holding back
the curse with her psychic powers.
Then let's get to it...
...and perform the operation.
First, let us cut off the banana organ.
Stop it!
I still only have one testicle!
It seems that
I am the chosen one after all.
Let go of Takakura-sama!
I'm human, and he's a demon.
I know it's wrong,
but I can't hold these feelings back.
I'm going to save Takakura-sama from the hands
of the evil boss demon, Momo Ayase!
I told you, you're wrong!
EPISODE 9
MERGE! SERPO DOVER DEMON NESSIE!
Next episode,
"Merge! Serpo Dover Demon Nessie!"
Listen to me!